Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXXI. SYSTEM BOARDS
  - Sub-Series 250-17-13. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. New York District
    - New York District Board of Adjustment, 1949-1951 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - New York District Board of Adjustment, 1948-1949 (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - New York District Board of Adjustment, 1947 (Box 181, Folder 1)
      August-December 1947.
    - New York District Board of Adjustment, 1947 (Box 181, Folder 2)
      January-July 1947.
    - New York District Board of Adjustment, 1944 (Box 181, Folder 3)
      1944 July 6. Subject: Special Meeting
    - New York District Board of Adjustment, 1922-1928 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - New York District Board of Adjustment, 1947 (Box 181, Folder 5)
      1947 July 28. Subject: Special Meeting
    - New York District Board of Adjustment, 1932-1935 (Box 181, Folder 6)
      Subject: Thomas Griffin
    - New York District Board of Adjustment, 1932-1935 (Box 181, Folder 7)
      Subject: Thomas E. Derrick
    - New York District Board of Adjustment, 1929-1933 (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 250-17-14. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. South Pacific Department District
    - South Pacific Department District Board of Adjustment, 1951-1961 (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - South Pacific Department District Board of Adjustment, 1924-1950 (Box 181, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 250-17-15. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. Southwestern Department District
    - Southwestern Department District Board of Adjustment, 1958-1962 (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - Southwestern Department District Board of Adjustment, 1954-1957 (Box 181, Folder 12)
    - Southwestern Department District Board of Adjustment, 1925-1953 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 250-17-16. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. Northern Pacific District
    - Northern Pacific District Board of Adjustment, 1951-1962 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Northern Pacific District Board of Adjustment, 1923-1950 (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 250-17-17. System Boards: Express Boards of Adjustment. Southeastern Express Division District
    - Southeastern Express Division District Board of Adjustment, 1926-1930 (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 250-18. System Boards. Southern Pacific
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1963 (Box 182, Folder 5)
      Subject: Protest of Election of General Chairman
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1961-1963 (Box 182, Folder 6)
      Subject: Appeal of S.S. Stein
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1965 (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1963 (Box 182, Folder 8)
      January-October 1963.
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1961-1962 (Box 182, Folder 9)
      September 1961-62.
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1961 (Box 182, Folder 10)
      June 1960-September 14, 1961.
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1960 (Box 182, Folder 11)
      January 1959-May 1960.
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1958 (Box 182, Folder 12)
      April 1957-58.
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1950-1957 (Box 182, Folder 13)
      August 1950-March 1957.
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1956 (Box 183, Folder 1)
      September 1955-July 1956.
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1955 (Box 183, Folder 2)
      1954-August 1955.
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1952-1953 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1946-1951 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1945 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1940-1943 (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1930-1939 (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1929 (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1957 (Box 183, Folder 9)
      Subject: Dispute Los Angeles Union Passenger Terminal
    - Southern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1941 (Box 183, Folder 10)
      March 17-21, 1941. Subject: Minutes of Twenty-Third Annual Meeting
  - Sub-Series 250-19. System Boards. Union Pacific
    - Union Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1966 (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - Union Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1965 (Box 183, Folder 12)
    - Union Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1964 (Box 183, Folder 13)
    - Union Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1961-1962 (Box 183, Folder 14)
    - Union Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1959 (Box 184, Folder 1)
      Subject: Salary and Expense Payments
    - Union Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1960 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - Union Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1958 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Union Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1956 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Union Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1954 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Union Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1951 (Box 184, Folder 6)
      December 1948-July 1951.
    - Union Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1946-1947 (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - Union Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1946-1949 (Box 184, Folder 8)
      Subject: Leo Cunningham Case
    - Union Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1947 (Box 184, Folder 9)
      1947 December 16. Subject: Hearing
    - Union Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1947 (Box 184, Folder 10)
    - Union Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1947 (Box 184, Folder 11)
      1947 December 4. Subject: Hearing
    - Union Pacific (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1948 (Box 184, Folder 12)
      January-August 1948.
    - Union Pacific (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1964 (Box 184, Folder 13)
    - Union Pacific (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1953-1962 (Box 184, Folder 14)
      June 1953-62.
    - Union Pacific (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1946-1953 (Box 184, Folder 15)
      1946-May 1953.
    - Union Pacific (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1933-1945 (Box 184, Folder 16)
    - Union Pacific (Lines West) System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1932 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 250-20. System Boards. Pennsylvania
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1949-1950 (Box 185, Folder 2)
      1949-February 14, 1950. Subject: E.A. Smith
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1950-1952 (Box 185, Folder 3)
      February 15, 1950-52. Subject: E.A. Smith
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1952-1953 (Box 185, Folder 4)
      1952-August 1953.
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1951 (Box 185, Folder 5)
      October-December 1951.
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1950 (Box 185, Folder 6)
      November 1948-April 1950.
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1948 (Box 185, Folder 7)
      May-October 1948.
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1945-1948 (Box 185, Folder 8)
      August 1945-April 1948.
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1940-1945 (Box 185, Folder 9)
      1940-July 1945.
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1926-1939 (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1938-1939 (Box 185, Folder 11)
      Subject: Division Chairman, New York Division
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1925 (Box 185, Folder 12)
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1922 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1921 (Box 186, Folder 2)
      September-December 1921.
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1921 (Box 186, Folder 3)
      June-August 1921.
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1958 (Box 186, Folder 4)
      Subject: T.R. Zawada vs. System Board
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1965 (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1964 (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1960 (Box 186, Folder 7)
      Subject: T.R. Zawada
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1962 (Box 186, Folder 8)
      February-December 1962.
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1961-1962 (Box 186, Folder 9)
      February 1961-January 1962.
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1961 (Box 186, Folder 10)
      September 1959-January 1961.
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1959 (Box 187, Folder 1)
      Subject: Legal Expenses
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1959 (Box 187, Folder 2)
      May 1957-August 1959.
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1957 (Box 187, Folder 3)
      October 1955-April 1957.
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1955 (Box 187, Folder 4)
      July 1954-September 1955.
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1953-1954 (Box 187, Folder 5)
      September 1953-June 1954.
  - Sub-Series 250-21. System Boards. Great Northern
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1963 (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1962-1963 (Box 187, Folder 7)
      Subject: Appeal W.J. Lamb
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1961-1962 (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1961 (Box 187, Folder 9)
      March 1960-August 1961.
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1960 (Box 187, Folder 10)
      September 1957-February 1960.
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1957 (Box 187, Folder 11)
      1956-August 1957.
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1955 (Box 187, Folder 12)
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1952-1953 (Box 188, Folder 1)
      July 1952-53.
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1950-1952 (Box 188, Folder 2)
      June 14, 1950-June 1952.
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1952 (Box 188, Folder 3)
      Subject: Dispute of Lodges 340 and 434 and Willmar Division Protective Committee
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1949-1950 (Box 188, Folder 4)
      1949-June 13, 1950.
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1948 (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1946 (Box 188, Folder 6)
      Subject: Minutes
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1926-1937 (Box 188, Folder 7)
      June 1926-37.
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1925-1926 (Box 188, Folder 8)
      October 1925-June 1926.
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1925 (Box 188, Folder 9)
      1922-September 1925.
  - Sub-Series 250-22. System Boards. Northern Pacific
    - Northern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1962 (Box 188, Folder 10)
      1957-April 1962.
    - Northern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1952-1957 (Box 189, Folder 1)
      August 1952-January 3, 1957.
    - Northern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1952 (Box 189, Folder 2)
      1951-June 1952.
    - Northern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1950 (Box 189, Folder 3)
      November 1948-50.
    - Northern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1946-1948 (Box 189, Folder 4)
      September 1946-October 1948.
    - Northern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1946 (Box 189, Folder 5)
      1944-August 1946.
    - Northern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1945 (Box 189, Folder 6)
      1945 June 12. Subject: Minutes
    - Northern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1927-1943 (Box 189, Folder 7)
      November 27, 1927-43.
    - Northern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1927 (Box 189, Folder 8)
      November 21-26, 1927.
    - Northern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1927 (Box 189, Folder 9)
      1921-November 20, 1927.
  - Sub-Series 250-23. System Boards. Texas and Pacific
    - Texas and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1962 (Box 189, Folder 10)
      April 1959-May 1962.
    - Texas and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1959 (Box 190, Folder 1)
      March 1957-March 1959.
    - Texas and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1957 (Box 190, Folder 2)
      May 1955-February 1957.
    - Texas and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1955 (Box 190, Folder 3)
      1954-April 1955.
    - Texas and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1953 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Texas and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1950-1952 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Texas and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1940-1949 (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - Texas and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1939 (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 250-24. System Boards. Soo Line
    - Soo Line System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1964 (Box 190, Folder 8)
      May 7, 1960-64. Consolidated with System Board No. 154, Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range System Board of Adjustment, effective October 16, 1962
    - Soo Line System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1960 (Box 190, Folder 9)
      March 1958-May 6, 1960. Consolidated with System Board No. 154, Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range System Board of Adjustment, effective October 16, 1962
    - Soo Line System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1958 (Box 190, Folder 10)
      February 1956-February 1958. Consolidated with System Board No. 154, Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range System Board of Adjustment, effective October 16, 1962
    - Soo Line System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1956 (Box 190, Folder 11)
      April 1951-January 1956. Consolidated with System Board No. 154, Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range System Board of Adjustment, effective October 16, 1962
    - Soo Line System Board of Adjustment, 1943-1951 (Box 190, Folder 12)
      1943-March 1951. Consolidated with System Board No. 154, Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range System Board of Adjustment, effective October 16, 1962
    - Soo Line System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1942 (Box 190, Folder 13)
      Consolidated with System Board No. 154, Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range System Board of Adjustment, effective October 16, 1962
  - Sub-Series 250-25. System Boards. Missouri-Kansas-Texas
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1968 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1959 (Box 191, Folder 2)
      May 1957-59.
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1957 (Box 191, Folder 3)
      1955-April 1957.
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas System Board of Adjustment, 1952-1954 (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1951 (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas System Board of Adjustment, 1951 (Box 191, Folder 6)
      1951 May 18. Subject: Minutes
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas System Board of Adjustment, 1950 (Box 191, Folder 7)
      1950 May 14. Subject: Minutes
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1947 (Box 191, Folder 8)
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas System Board of Adjustment, 1947 (Box 191, Folder 9)
      1947 March 16. Subject: Minutes
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas System Board of Adjustment, 1946 (Box 191, Folder 10)
      1946 April 7. Subject: Minutes
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas System Board of Adjustment, 1932-1943 (Box 191, Folder 11)
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1931 (Box 191, Folder 12)
      July 1922-August 1931.
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1922 (Box 191, Folder 13)
      1921-June 1922.
  - Sub-Series 250-26. System Boards. Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1958 (Box 191, Folder 14)
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1954 (Box 191, Folder 15)
      May 1951-54.
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1951 (Box 191, Folder 16)
      1948-April 1951.
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1947 (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1933-1943 (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1934-1935 (Box 192, Folder 3)
      Subject: Charles A. Joyce
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1920-1932 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 250-27. System Boards. St. Louis Southwestern
    - St. Louis Southwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - St. Louis Southwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1959 (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - St. Louis Southwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1953-1955 (Box 192, Folder 7)
      July 1953-55.
    - St. Louis Southwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1950-1953 (Box 192, Folder 8)
      1950-June 1953.
    - St. Louis Southwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1949 (Box 192, Folder 9)
    - St. Louis Southwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1940-1943 (Box 192, Folder 10)
    - St. Louis Southwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1939 (Box 192, Folder 11)
    - St. Louis Southwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1939 (Box 192, Folder 12)
      September 17-18, 1939. Subject: Minutes
  - Sub-Series 250-28. System Boards. Chesapeake and Ohio
    - Chesapeake and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1965 (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1964 (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1963 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1962 (Box 193, Folder 4)
      December 1958-62.
    - Chesapeake and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1958 (Box 193, Folder 5)
      January 12, 1957-November 1958.
    - Chesapeake and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1955-1957 (Box 193, Folder 6)
      July 7, 1955-January 11, 1957.
    - Chesapeake and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1955 (Box 193, Folder 7)
      September 1951-July 6, 1955.
    - Chesapeake and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1951 (Box 193, Folder 8)
      1944-August 1951.
    - Chesapeake and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1943 (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1938 (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1935 (Box 193, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-29. System Boards. Western Pacific
    - Western Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1962 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Western Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1956 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 250-30. System Boards. Reading
    - Reading System Board of Adjustment, 1965 (Box 194, Folder 3)
      September-December 1965.
    - Reading System Board of Adjustment, 1962-1965 (Box 194, Folder 4)
      August 16, 1962-September 1965.
    - Reading System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 194, Folder 5)
      1960-August 15, 1962.
    - Reading System Board of Adjustment, 1959 (Box 194, Folder 6)
      October-December 1959.
    - Reading System Board of Adjustment, 1957-1959 (Box 194, Folder 7)
      1957-September 1959.
    - Reading System Board of Adjustment, 1953-1956 (Box 194, Folder 8)
      August 1953-56.
    - Reading System Board of Adjustment, 1950-1953 (Box 194, Folder 9)
      July 1950-July 1953.
    - Reading System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1950 (Box 194, Folder 10)
      1948-June 1950.
    - Reading System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1947 (Box 194, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 250-31. System Boards. Baltimore and Ohio
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1965 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1962-1964 (Box 195, Folder 2)
      September 16, 1962-64.
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 195, Folder 3)
      July 1960-September 15, 1962.
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1958-1960 (Box 195, Folder 4)
      1958-June 1960.
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1957 (Box 195, Folder 5)
      August 1956-57.
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1956 (Box 195, Folder 6)
      August 1954-July 1956.
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1952-1954 (Box 195, Folder 7)
      June 1952-July 1954.
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1950-1952 (Box 195, Folder 8)
      March 1950-May 1952.
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1947 (Box 195, Folder 9)
      June 16-, 1947. Subject: Minutes
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1947-1950 (Box 195, Folder 10)
      1947-Feburary 1950.
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1946 (Box 195, Folder 11)
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1930-1938 (Box 195, Folder 12)
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1928 (Box 195, Folder 13)
      1928 January. Subject: "Editorial on Centenary of B&O Railroad Company"
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1927-1929 (Box 195, Folder 14)
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1925 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Baltimore and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1922 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 250-32. System Boards. Chicago and Alton
    - Chicago and Alton System Board of Adjustment, 1930-1946 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Chicago and Alton System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1928 (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 250-34. System Boards. Pere Marquette
    - Pere Marquette System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Pere Marquette System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1959 (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Pere Marquette System Board of Adjustment, 1936-1953 (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - Pere Marquette System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1935 (Box 196, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 250-35. System Boards. Frisco
    - Frisco System Board of Adjustment, 1964 (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - Frisco System Board of Adjustment, 1962-1963 (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - Frisco System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1962 (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - Frisco System Board of Adjustment, 1956-1958 (Box 196, Folder 12)
    - Frisco System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1955 (Box 196a, Folder 1)
      August 1951-55.
    - Frisco System Board of Adjustment, 1937-1951 (Box 196a, Folder 2)
      1937-July 1951.
    - Frisco System Board of Adjustment, 1936 (Box 196a, Folder 3)
    - Frisco System Board of Adjustment, 1933-1935 (Box 196a, Folder 4)
    - Frisco System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1932 (Box 196a, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 250-36. System Boards. Kansas City Terminal
    - Kansas City Terminal System Board of Adjustment, 1963-1965 (Box 196a, Folder 6)
    - Kansas City Terminal System Board of Adjustment, 1960-1962 (Box 196a, Folder 7)
    - Kansas City Terminal System Board of Adjustment, 1953-1959 (Box 196a, Folder 8)
      July 1953-59.
    - Kansas City Terminal System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1953 (Box 196a, Folder 9)
      1922-June 1953.
  - Sub-Series 250-37. System Boards. Union Depot (Columbus, Ohio)
    - Union Depot (Columbus, Ohio) System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1951 (Box 196a, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 250-38-E. System Boards. New York Central (Lines East)
    - New York Central (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1964-1965 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - New York Central (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1962-1963 (Box 197, Folder 2)
      June 1962-63.
    - New York Central (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1959-1963 (Box 197, Folder 3)
      1959-May 1963.
    - New York Central (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1954-1958 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - New York Central (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1958 (Box 197, Folder 5)
      Subject: Home Study